Contact

Santo André SP (11) 997572385 (Mobile) igorneysantos@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/igor-santosufabc (LinkedIn) github.com/igorney (Other)

Top Skills

Terraform
MySQL
Continuous Integration

Certifications

AWS Academy Graduate - AWS Academy Cloud Foundations SQL (Basic) Certificate AWS Academy Cloud Developing Python (Basic) AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Igor Santos

Software Engineer | Computer Science | AWS Certified | Back-End Developer | Solutions Architect

Santo André, São Paulo, Brazil

Summary

Computer Science student working as a Software Engineer. I have experience with distributed systems, microservices, MQ queues, Pub/Sub Kafka, container platforms using kubernetes like openshift. Still, I have experience with AWS services and solutions. Iac like terraform, Devops and Ci/Cd using github and github actions. I really like learning new things and working with different areas. I'm always willing to teach and face new challenges!

Experience

Itaú Unibanco 3 years 5 months Junior Software Developer August 2021 - Present (2 years) São Paulo, São Paulo, Brasil

Software Intern March 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 6 months) São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil

KUKA Systems do Brasil Software Intern May 2019 - January 2020 (9 months) São Paulo Area, Brazil

Education

Universidade Federal do ABC

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (June 2018 - December 2024)

ETEC Jorge Street

Ensino Técnico, Tecnologia em Informática/Software · (2016 - 2017)

Page 1 of 2

EME Prof.ª Alcina Dantas Feijão

Ensino Médio · (2015 - 2017)